<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<module suppressWarnings="true">

<User f="nodata">
    <User f="noscroll">
        <Select_User t="list" f="user"/>
        <Login t="button" l="Control"/>
    </User>
</User>

<Control f="nodata">
    <Main f="noscroll">
        <New_Cafe t="button" l="Cafe"/>
        <Existing_Cafes t="list" e="Cafe"/> 
    </Main>
    <Defaults>
        <autonum/>
        <GPS_Diagnostics t="gpsdiag"/>
    </Defaults>
    <search>
    Search Records
    </search>
</Control>

<Cafe>
    <fmt>{{Cafe_ID}}-{{Cafe_Name}}-{{Street_Name}}</fmt>
    <About_Cafe>
        <cols>
            <author>
            Created by
            </author>
            <timestamp>
            Created at
            </timestamp>    
        </cols>
        <cols>
            <Cafe_ID f="notnull autonum" t="input">
                <desc>Cafe's unique ID number, autoincremented by 1</desc>
            </Cafe_ID>
            <Cafe_Name f="notnull" t="input">
            <desc>Name of the Cafe, as seen above / near the main entrance, inside the cafe or on the menu.</desc>
            </Cafe_Name>
        </cols>
        <cols>
            <Street_Name f="notnull" t="input">
                <desc>Enter Street name e.g. Clarence Street.</desc>
            </Street_Name>
            <Street_Number f="notnull" b="decimal">
            <desc>Enter Street number.</desc>
            </Street_Number>
        </cols>
        <cols>
            <City f="notnull" t="input">
                <desc>Enter name of the City.</desc>
            </City>
            <State t="input">
                <desc>Enter name of the State.</desc>
            </State>
        </cols>
        <gps/>
        <Take_Representative_Photo_of_the_Cafe t="camera">
            <desc>Photo of Cafe</desc>
        </Take_Representative_Photo_of_the_Cafe>
        <cols>
            <Opening_Hours_Weekday t="checkbox">
            <desc>Check all the hours of the day when the Cafe is open during a regular weekday, using 24h format</desc>
            <opts>
                <opt> 6:00 </opt>
                <opt> 7:00 </opt>
                <opt> 8:00 </opt>
                <opt> 9:00 </opt>
                <opt> 10:00 </opt>
                <opt> 11:00 </opt>
                <opt> 12:00 </opt>
                <opt> 13:00 </opt>
                <opt> 14:00 </opt>
                <opt> 15:00 </opt>
                <opt> 16:00 </opt>
                <opt> 17:00 </opt>
                <opt> 18:00 </opt>
                <opt> 19:00 </opt>
                <opt> 20:00 </opt>
            </opts>
            </Opening_Hours_Weekday>
            <Opening_Hours_Weekend t="checkbox">
            <desc>Check all the hours of the day when the Cafe is open during a regular weekend, using 24h format</desc>
            <opts>
                <opt> 6:00 </opt>
                <opt> 7:00 </opt>
                <opt> 8:00 </opt>
                <opt> 9:00 </opt>
                <opt> 10:00 </opt>
                <opt> 11:00 </opt>
                <opt> 12:00 </opt>
                <opt> 13:00 </opt>
                <opt> 14:00 </opt>
                <opt> 15:00 </opt>
                <opt> 16:00 </opt>
                <opt> 17:00 </opt>
                <opt> 18:00 </opt>
                <opt> 19:00 </opt>
                <opt> 20:00 </opt>
            </opts>
            </Opening_Hours_Weekend>
        </cols>
        <Contact t="input">
            <desc>Write down a telephone number, website, Twitter account, Facebook page or any other mean of contact.</desc>
        </Contact>      
    </About_Cafe>
    <Coffee_Review f="noscroll">
        <Add_Review t="button" lc="Coffee"/>
        <Existing_Reviews t="list" ec="Coffee"/>
    </Coffee_Review>
</Cafe>

<Coffee>
    <fmt>{{Cafe_Name_Review}}-{{Review_ID}} R: {{Coffee_Rating}}</fmt>
    <Review>
        <cols>
            <Review_ID f="notnull autonum">
              <desc>Review's unique ID, autoincremented by 1</desc>
            </Review_ID>
            <Cafe_Name_Review f="notnull" i="Cafe/About_Cafe/Cafe_Name">
            </Cafe_Name_Review>
        </cols>
        <cols>
            <author>
            Created by
            </author>
            <timestamp>
            Created at
            </timestamp>
        </cols>
        <cols>
         <Coffee_Beans t="dropdown">
            <desc>Origin of used coffee beans.</desc>
                <opts>
                    <opt>Brazil</opt>
                    <opt>Colombia</opt>
                    <opt>Costa Rica</opt>
                    <opt>Guatemala</opt>
                    <opt>Ethiopia</opt>
                    <opt>Honduras</opt>
                    <opt>Indonesia</opt>
                    <opt>Kenya</opt>
                    <opt>Vietnam</opt>
                    <opt>Venezuela</opt>
                    <opt>Other</opt>
                </opts>
        </Coffee_Beans>
        <Coffee_Roastery t="input">
            <desc>Name of the roastery.</desc>
        </Coffee_Roastery>
        </cols>
        <cols>
            <Coffee_Traditional t="checkbox">
            Traditional Espresso-based Coffee
                <desc>Choose the type of the traditional-style coffee you have ordered.</desc>
                <opts>
                    <opt>Americano
                        <desc>Americano style coffee is made with espresso (one or several shots), with hot water then added to give a similar strength (but different flavor) to drip-brewed coffee.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Cappuccino
                        <desc>Cappuccino comprises equal parts of espresso coffee and milk and froth, sometimes sprinkled with cinnamon or powdered cocoa.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Flat White
                        <desc>Flat white is one part espresso with two parts steamed milk, usually served in a cappuccino cup with the foam decorated with a motif (e.g., fern or heart). This is a speciality of Australia and New Zealand.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Latte
                        <desc>Caffè latte or caffè e latte is often called simply latte, which is Italian for ""milk"", in English-speaking countries; it is espresso with steamed milk, traditionally topped with froth created from steaming the milk. A latte comprises one-third espresso and nearly two-thirds steamed milk. More frothed milk makes it weaker than a cappuccino.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Long Black
                        <desc>Long black is similar to Americano, but prepared in different order (a double shot of espresso is added to water instead of vice versa); most common in Australia and New Zealand.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Mocha
                        <desc>Mocha is a latte with chocolate added.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Other</opt>
                </opts>
            </Coffee_Traditional>
            <Coffee_Alternative t="checkbox">
                Alternative Brewing styles
                <desc>Choose the type of alternative brewing style coffee you have ordered.</desc>
                <opts>
                    <opt>Aeropress
                        <desc>The AeroPress is a mechanical, non-electronic device where pressure is simply exerted by the user manually pressing a piston down with their hand, forcing medium-temperature water through coffee grounds in about 30 seconds (into a single cup.) This method produces a smoother beverage than espresso, falling somewhere between the flavor of a moka pot and a French Press.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Batchbrew
                        <desc>Very similar in taste and quality to Drip / Pourover coffee, but made in large quantities rather than one serving at the time.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Cold Brew
                        <desc>Cold brew coffee, sometimes known as "cold press." Cold water is poured over coffee grounds and allowed to steep for eight to twenty-four hours. The coffee is then filtered, usually through a very thick filter, removing all particles. This process produces a very strong concentrate which can be stored in a refrigerated, airtight container for up to eight weeks. The coffee prepared by this method is very low in acidity with a smooth taste, and is often preferred by those with sensitive stomachs. Others, however, feel this method strips coffee of its bold flavor and character. </desc></opt>
                    <opt>Drip or Pourover
                        <desc>Drip brewing, filtered coffee, or pour-over is a method which involves pouring water over roasted, ground coffee beans contained in a filter, creating the beverage called coffee. Water seeps through the ground coffee, absorbing its oils and essences, solely under gravity, then passes through the bottom of the filter. The used coffee grounds are retained in the filter with the liquid falling (dripping) into a collecting vessel such as a carafe or pot.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>French Press
                        <desc>The French press goes by various names around the world. In Italy the press is known as a caffettiera a stantuffo. A French press requires coffee of a coarser grind than does a drip brew coffee filter, as finer grounds, when immersed in water, have lower permeability than coarser grounds, requiring an excessive and potentially dangerous amount of force to be applied by hand to lower the plunger. It is widely believed that the optimum time for brewing the coffee is around 4 minutes. Others consider the coffee spoiled after about 20 minutes. Other approaches, such as cold-brewing, require several hours of contact between the water and the grounds to achieve the desired extraction.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Moka Pot
                        <desc> The moka pot, also known as the "Italian coffeepot" or the "caffettiera" is a three-chamber design which boils water in the lower section. The generated steam pressure, about one bar (100 kPa, 14.5 psi), forces the boiling water up through coffee grounds held in the middle section, separated by a filter mesh from the top section. The resultant coffee (almost espresso strength, but without the crema) is collected in the top section. Moka pots usually sit directly on a stovetop heater or burner. Some models have a transparent glass or plastic top.</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Vacuum Pot
                        <desc> A vacuum coffee maker brews coffee using two chambers where vapor pressure and vacuum produce coffee. A vacuum coffee maker operates as a siphon, where heating and cooling the lower vessel changes the vapor pressure of water in the lower, first pushing the water up into the upper vessel, then allowing the water to fall back down into the lower vessel. Concretely, the principle of a vacuum coffee maker is to heat water in the lower vessel of the brewer until expansion forces the contents through a narrow tube into an upper vessel containing coffee grounds (as water temperature increases, dense liquid water increasingly converts to less dense water vapor gas, which takes up more space and thus increases pressure); when the water reaches and exceeds the boiling point (so the vapor pressure equals and then exceeds atmospheric pressure), the (water vapor) pressure in the lower vessel exceeds the (atmospheric) pressure in the top vessel and water is pushed up the siphon tube into the upper vessel."</desc></opt>
                    <opt>Other</opt>
                </opts>
            </Coffee_Alternative>
        </cols>
            <Coffee_Rating f="notnull" t="radio">
            Coffee Rating (1 - worst; 5 - best)
            <desc>Rate the overall experience of ordered coffee: 1 - undrinkable; 5 - the best coffee of my life.</desc>
            <opts>
                <opt>1</opt>
                <opt>1.5</opt>
                <opt>2</opt>
                <opt>2.5</opt>
                <opt>3</opt>
                <opt>3.5</opt>
                <opt>4</opt>
                <opt>4.5</opt>
                <opt>5</opt>
            </opts>
        </Coffee_Rating>
        <Coffee_Comments t="input">
            <desc>Comment on the coffee.</desc>
        </Coffee_Comments>
        <Revisit_Recommendations t="radio">
            Would you like to come back?
            <desc>Would you like to come back?</desc>
            <opts>
                <opt>Yes</opt>
                <opt>Maybe</opt>
                <opt>No</opt>
            </opts>
        </Revisit_Recommendations>
        <Take_Coffee_Photo t="camera">
            <desc>Take Picture of the ordered coffee.</desc>
        </Take_Coffee_Photo>
        <Choose_Photo_from_Device t="file">
            <desc>Choose Photo from Device, using external apps. First you have to navigate to the folder where the file you want to attach lives and then attach it.</desc>
        </Choose_Photo_from_Device>  
    </Review>
</Coffee>

</module>
